[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "In case I ___ what to buy, I will make a shopping list.",
        "answer": "forget"
    },
    {
        "question": "They ___ their homework by the time their parents come back.",
        "answer": "will have finished"
    },
    {
        "question": "The dog ___ his food until it sees its owner.",
        "answer": "won’t eat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which conditional form does the sentence use?I will visit you as soon as I arrive.",
        "answer": "first conditional"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which conditional form does the sentence use?I’ll call you after I get home.",
        "answer": "first conditional"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sophie will buy some souvenirs before she ___ Japan.",
        "answer": "leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which conditional form does the sentence use?Plants die if you don’t water them.",
        "answer": "zero conditional"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which conditional form does the sentence use?If the temperature drops to 0°, water freezes.",
        "answer": "zero conditional"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which conditional form does the sentence use?My sister will stay at a friend’s house if she finishes work late.",
        "answer": "first conditional"
    },
    {
        "question": "She ___ a movie with us if she gets paid this afternoon.",
        "answer": "will go to"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which conditional form does the sentence use?If she wants to be in shape, she has to exercise regularly.",
        "answer": "zero conditional"
    },
    {
        "question": "My father will call me after he ___ at his hotel.",
        "answer": "checks in"
    },
    {
        "question": "Nancy ___ better as soon as she has a cup of black tea.",
        "answer": "will feel"
    },
    {
        "question": "You ___ if you don’t wear a mask in public.",
        "answer": "can be fined"
    },
    {
        "question": "My mother won’t give me any pocket money unless I ___ my room weekly.",
        "answer": "clean"
    },
    {
        "question": "If she gets eight hours of sleep, she usually ___ alert.",
        "answer": "feels"
    },
    {
        "question": "I will get some gas now ___ the price goes up later.",
        "answer": "in case"
    },
    {
        "question": "As soon as they ___ the English exam, they will go to America.",
        "answer": "pass"
    },
    {
        "question": "If Joe ___ the book, I will lend it to him.",
        "answer": "hasn’t read"
    }
]